http://www.falconindustries.com/privacy

Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Our Products
Helicoid Flight
Helicoid flight is a continuous one-piece helix formed from square or rectangle bar, round bar or cut plate.
Sectional Flight
Sectional flights are individual turns, wraps, or segments of wraps formed into a helix.
Ribbon Flight
Ribbon flight is a continuous, large diameter one-piece helix formed from bar or cut plate.
Shaftless Flight
Shaftless flight is heavier gauge helicoid flight that is produced to outside diameter and pitch specifications with an open center. This product works well when moving sticky products and large sized lumps.
Complete Screws
Falcon has the machining and assembly capabilities to manufacture the most complicated and demanding conveyor augers and mixing screws to our customers’ specifications.  Complete screw weldments or augers are produced by mounting helical or sectional flight to a shaft, pipe, flange, hub, posts or other means to turn the screw.
Maintenance & Repairs
One of the inherent problems associated with conveyor screws, augers and auger flighting is wear.  Falcon’s experience and expertise saves our customers time and money by repairing existing assemblies rather than building new.
Get a Quote
Please select the service or product you'd like a quote for and a representative from Falcon Industries, Inc. will contact you shortly to help you fulfill your request.
Helicoid Flight
Sectional Flight
Ribbon Flight
Shaftless Flight
Complete Screws
Maintenance & Repairs
Get Quote
If you'd like to speak with someone, please call (888) 993-2526.
Thank you!
A Lesson Trump and the E.P.A. Should Heed https://t.co/YbC2a3egKA
3 years ago
Lots to learn about Abrasion Resistant Steels.
Check it out: https://t.co/CylwmsyPCq
4 years ago
Stuck in summer construction traffic.. but at least I get to watch an auger in action!
https://t.co/kxxeSw4e6x https://t.co/8LJjpyQJBQ
4 years ago
Innovative design in auger drives https://t.co/nAMkyzwLOf
4 years ago
About Us
Falcon is a premier supplier of custom augers and auger flighting.  We form flight out of a wide variety of materials for industries all over the world, making conveyor and mixing screws, ribbon flighting and various other helicoid and sectional flighting.  Our products are manufactured to our customers’ individual specifications and designs, ensuring our customers receive the precise product required for their needs and equipment.  Our products are used domestically and internationally.
Read More
Address
For Eastern North America & International Falcon Industries, Inc.
180 Commerce Drive, Medina, OH 44256
PH: (330) 723-0099, FAX: (330) 723-5399
Toll Free: (888) 993-2526
Medina at FalconIndustries.com
For Western North America Falcon Industries, Inc.
901 Astro Boulevard East,
Cosmos, MN 56228, PH: (320) 877-7713, FAX: (320) 877-7715
Toll Free: (888) 993-2526
Cosmos at FalconIndustries.com
Additional Links
Company AwardsNews ArchiveTerms & ConditionsPrivacy Falcon Quality Policy
Product Gallery
WRIS Web Services: Manufacturing
HomeProductsIndustriesTestimonialsAboutQuoteContact
